import { Deck } from '@/types/Card';

export const MockData: Deck = {
  title: 'JavaScript Libraries',
  subtitle: 'Library Descriptions',
  cards: [
    {
      front: 'A library for building user interfaces with reusable components.',
      back: 'React',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library for creating interactive user interfaces with a focus on data binding.',
      back: 'Angular',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A framework for building server-rendered applications using Vue.js.',
      back: 'Nuxt.js',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A lightweight JavaScript library for creating dynamic, interactive user interfaces.',
      back: 'jQuery',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library for managing and manipulating state in a predictable way in JavaScript applications.',
      back: 'Redux',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library that provides a flexible way to create forms and handle form state.',
      back: 'Formik',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A framework for building full-stack web applications with server-side rendering.',
      back: 'Next.js',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library for functional programming in JavaScript, providing utility functions for common programming tasks.',
      back: 'Lodash',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A lightweight JavaScript library for managing asynchronous operations with promises.',
      back: 'Axios',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library that helps in creating and managing animations and transitions.',
      back: 'Framer Motion',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library for creating, validating, and managing forms in React applications.',
      back: 'React Hook Form',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library that provides utility functions for handling dates and times.',
      back: 'date-fns',
    },
    {
      front: 'A library for handling routing in React applications.',
      back: 'React Router',
    },
    {
      front:
        'A library for creating responsive layouts using a grid system and utility classes.',
      back: 'Bootstrap',
    },
  ],
};
